https://polezero.com/privacy-policy-and-cookies-usage/

Privacy policy and cookies usage
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors – this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information
What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information.
Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including Names, Job Title, Company Name, Email Address, Telephone Number, Country, Interests).
Any other information that you choose to send to us.
Cookies
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser.
The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We use session cookies on the website. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. We will use the session cookies for the following purposes: To prevent accidental contact form resubmissions.
Third parties who provide web services to us may also send you cookies.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at:
http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html
Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking Tools, Internet Options, Privacy, and selecting Block all cookies using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites.
Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happywith any changes.
Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
Using your personal information
Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information for the following purposes.
To enable your use of the services available on the website.
To send to you marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications).
To deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.
Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees and subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.In addition, we may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances.
To the extent that we are required to disclose information by law. In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings.
In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
Security of your personal information
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password and firewall protected) servers.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to:
the payment of a fee (fixed by law at the date of writing at GBP 10.00); and
the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).
We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.
You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.
Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to info@smartway2.com or by post to: Smartway2, 26-28 Hammersmith Grove, London W6 7BA, United Kingdom
SOLUTIONS
WHY SMARTWAY2 MEETING ROOM BOOKING DESK BOOKING OUTLOOK ROOM BOOKING MOBILE RESOURCE BOOKING VISITOR MANAGEMENT MEETING ROOM DISPLAYS
RESOURCES
EBOOKS WEBINARS WHITE PAPERS BLOG
CONTACT US
SEND MESSAGE REQUEST DEMO CUSTOMER SUPPORT
LEGAL
PRIVACY POLICY TERMS OF SERVICE
CALL NOW
UNITED STATES
+1 (857) 284 8160
UNITED KINGDOM
+44 (0)1494 230 036
AUSTRALIA
+61 (2) 9959 1002
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
